[
     {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 54?",
      "correctAnswer": "2916",
      "options": [
        "2918",
        "2921",
        "2914",
        "2916"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 68?",
      "correctAnswer": "4624",
      "options": [
        "4629",
        "4622",
        "4626",
        "4624"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 22?",
      "correctAnswer": "484",
      "options": [
        "484",
        "489",
        "486",
        "482"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 77?",
      "correctAnswer": "5929",
      "options": [
        "5931",
        "5929",
        "5934",
        "5927"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 65?",
      "correctAnswer": "4225",
      "options": [
        "4227",
        "4230",
        "4225",
        "4223"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 47?",
      "correctAnswer": "2209",
      "options": [
        "2211",
        "2207",
        "2214",
        "2209"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 62?",
      "correctAnswer": "3844",
      "options": [
        "3849",
        "3844",
        "3842",
        "3846"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 63?",
      "correctAnswer": "3969",
      "options": [
        "3974",
        "3971",
        "3969",
        "3967"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 63?",
      "correctAnswer": "3969",
      "options": [
        "3974",
        "3971",
        "3969",
        "3967"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 77?",
      "correctAnswer": "5929",
      "options": [
        "5931",
        "5929",
        "5927",
        "5934"
      ]
    }
]